const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      category: "Characters",
      question: "What is Michael's middle name?",
      options: ["Gary", "George", "Gregory", "Gareth"],
      answer: "Gary",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      category: "Events",
      question: "What is the name of the company that acquires Dunder Mifflin?",
      options: ["Staples", "Sabre", "OfficeMax", "W.B. Mason"],
      answer: "Sabre",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      category: "Quotes",
      question: "Who said, 'I'm not superstitious, but I am a little stitious'?",
      options: ["Michael Scott", "Dwight Schrute", "Jim Halpert", "Pam Beesly"],
      answer: "Michael Scott",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      category: "Episode Titles",
      question: "In which episode does Michael burn his foot on a George Foreman Grill?",
      options: ["The Injury", "Diversity Day", "Casino Night", "The Dundies"],
      answer: "The Injury",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      category: "Characters",
      question: "What is the name of Angela's cat that Dwight kills?",
      options: ["Bandit", "Sprinkles", "Fluffy", "Whiskers"],
      answer: "Sprinkles",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      category: "Characters",
      question: "Who is the Regional Manager of the Utica branch?",
      options: ["Karen Filippelli", "David Wallace", "Jan Levinson", "Holly Flax"],
      answer: "Karen Filippelli",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      category: "Characters",
      question: "What is the name of Pam and Jim's first child?",
      options: ["Cecelia", "Philip", "Michael", "Angela"],
      answer: "Cecelia",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      category: "Characters",
      question: "Who started the fire in the office?",
      options: ["Michael Scott", "Dwight Schrute", "Ryan Howard", "Kevin Malone"],
      answer: "Ryan Howard",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      category: "Characters",
      question: "What is the name of Dwight's cousin?",
      options: ["Mose", "Rolf", "Zeke", "Gabor"],
      answer: "Mose",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      category: "Events",
      question: "What is the annual awards ceremony hosted by Michael called?",
      options: ["The Dundies", "The Michael Scott Awards", "The Dunder Awards", "The Scrantonies"],
      answer: "The Dundies",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      category: "Events",
      question: "What is the name of the event where employees can voice their complaints?",
      options: ["Complaint Hour", "Grievance Gathering", "Airing of Grievances", "Office Council"],
      answer: "Airing of Grievances",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      category: "Events",
      question: "What is the name of the annual office holiday party?",
      options: ["Christmas Bash", "Office Holiday Gala", "Dunder Mifflin Yuletide", "Party Planning Committee Party"],
      answer: "Dunder Mifflin Yuletide",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      category: "Events",
      question: "What event does Jim plan to propose to Pam before Andy proposes to Angela?",
      options: ["Toby's Farewell Party", "The Dundies", "Phyllis' Wedding", "Dunder Mifflin Beach Games"],
      answer: "Toby's Farewell Party",
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      category: "Quotes",
      question: "Who said, 'Bears, beets, Battlestar Galactica'?",
      options: ["Dwight Schrute", "Jim Halpert", "Michael Scott", "Stanley Hudson"],
      answer: "Jim Halpert",
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      category: "Quotes",
      question: "Who said, 'Identity theft is not a joke, Jim! Millions of families suffer every year!'?",
      options: ["Dwight Schrute", "Michael Scott", "Jim Halpert", "Pam Beesly"],
      answer: "Dwight Schrute",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      category: "Quotes",
      question: "Who said, 'I feel God in this Chili's tonight'?",
      options: ["Pam Beesly", "Michael Scott", "Dwight Schrute", "Kelly Kapoor"],
      answer: "Pam Beesly",
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      category: "Quotes",
      question: "Who said, 'I wish there was a way to know you're in the good old days before you've actually left them'?",
      options: ["Andy Bernard", "Jim Halpert", "Pam Beesly", "Michael Scott"],
      answer: "Andy Bernard",
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      category: "Episode Titles",
      question: "Which episode features Jim and Pam's wedding?",
      options: ["Niagara", "Weight Loss", "Finale", "Casino Night"],
      answer: "Niagara",
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      category: "Episode Titles",
      question: "Which episode involves a CPR training session?",
      options: ["Stress Relief", "Safety Training", "Health Care", "The Injury"],
      answer: "Stress Relief",
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      category: "Episode Titles",
      question: "Which episode is about the employees participating in a weight loss challenge?",
      options: ["Weight Loss", "The Surplus", "Branch Wars", "Beach Games"],
      answer: "Weight Loss",
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      category: "Episode Titles",
      question: "Which episode features Dwight's Christmas party as 'Belsnickel'?",
      options: ["Christmas Wishes", "A Benihana Christmas", "Dwight Christmas", "Moroccan Christmas"],
      answer: "Dwight Christmas",
    },
  ];
  
export default questions;
    